Guide to the Cormac McCarthy Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- The Stonemason, a play, 1985-1999, undated
  - Correspondence, 1993, 1997, undated
    - [Daniel Halpern, Ecco Press editor] to McCarthy. TLS, 1 page plus "interior layouts" and script page (6 leaves), October 29, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      Enclosing copyedited manuscript and sample pages. Requests a list of characters and a list of acts and scenes.
    - Janice Paran [McCarter dramaturg] to McCarthy. TLS, 3 pages with McCarthy's pencil notes, May 13, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Follow-up to earlier reading of The Stonemason with suggestions for alterations.
    - Jeffrey Woodward [McCarter managing director] to McCarthy. TLS, 2 pages plus McCarter contact sheet (2 leaves) and script page, May 21, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Letter serves as an agreement between the McCarter and McCarthy regarding the play, The Stonemason.
    - Emily Mann [McCarter director] to McCarthy. Facsimile, 5 pages with McCarthy's pencil notes, July 1, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      Consolidation of her and Janice's notes on the play.
    - McCarthy to Emily Mann. Photocopy, 2 pages, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
      "Here is the new version. I'll go over your letter. Changing the location of the drama is not something that would work for me…"
  - Notes, 1997, undated
    - Typescript pages with holograph corrections. 6 leaves plus manila folder marked "Stone Mason", undated (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Holograph and typescript pages. 16 leaves plus 1 newspaper clipping and pocket folder marked "Stonemason", undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Holograph and heavily corrected typescript pages. 38 leaves plus annotated manila folder, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Notes regarding McCarter production, including program, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      2 copies of McCarter program, June 20, 1997; one with pencil notes; 9 notebook paper pages with holograph notes; Photocopy pages numbered 2-45; 00 with minor holograph corrections; Manila folder marked "Stone Mason (inc new opening pp).
  - Drafts, 1985-1999, undated
    - Typescript, heavily corrected early draft with holograph note on first page, "Begun Thurs Feb 14." 83 leaves, circa 1985 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Photocopy of corrected draft with no holograph corrections. 110 leaves plus manila folder marked "S/Mason xrox – Arena Stage", undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Typescript first draft, heavily corrected. 113 pages (120 leaves) plus manila folder marked "Stonemason orig. ms.", undated (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Photocopy draft with no corrections. 102 pages (103 leaves) plus manila folder marked "S/Mason copy." Interior of folder contains notes re: West [Pretty Little Horses], undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Typescript of middle draft, heavily corrected. 106 pages (112 leaves), undated (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Photocopy of draft in box 66, folder 11 with fewer corrections. 106 pages (107 leaves) plus manila folder marked "S/Mason xerox – Arena", undated (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Typescript with holograph corrections. 102 pages (106 leaves), undated (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy of draft in box 67, folder 1, bound in ICM talent agency cover. No holograph corrections. 101 pages (missing p. 102), undated (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy of heavily corrected draft. No holograph corrections. 102 pages (110 leaves), undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Typescript, no corrections or page numbers. 108 leaves plus manila folder marked "(org) theatre version", undated (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Print out draft. The only pencil correction is on page 1. 152 pages (153 leaves) plus 3 copies of McCarter Theatre rehearsal program, June 20, 1997 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Print out draft, heavily corrected. 116 pages (128 leaves), undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Print out draft with title sheet and holograph corrections. 152 pages (153 leaves), March 1999 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Print out draft incorporating corrections from draft in box 67, folder 7. Contains additional holograph corrections. 150 pages (151 leaves), 1999 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      Cover letter from Emily Mann to McCarthy. TLS. 1 page April 20, 1999; McCarter Lab contact sheet, 2 pages, May 7, 1999; McCarter Theatre Lab schedule overview, 1 page, May 7, 1999; McCarter Theatre Lab rehearsal schedule, 1 page, May 7, 1999.
  - Fragments, circa 1985, undated
    - Typescript pages, early draft, heavily corrected]. No clear pagination; possibly from varying drafts. (82 leaves), circa 1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Corrected typescript page number 65. (1 leaf) plus manila folder marked "The Stonemason", undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy pages numbered 46-102, late draft. Minor pencil corrections. (58 leaves), undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Photocopy of corrected pages numbered 94-99; 110-130. (26 leaves), undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Proofs, 1993-1994, undated
    - Photocopy of corrected draft, with additional holograph corrections in red ink. 102 pages (118 leaves), undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Photocopy proofs, stamped "Master Set First Pass." No corrections. 133 pages (132 leaves), December 7, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Photocopy of corrected proofs, stamped "Master Set First Pass." No additional corrections. 133 pages (137 leaves), December 7, 1993
    - Photocopy of Ecco Press book with holograph corrections. 133 pages (70 leaves), undated (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Photocopy proofs, January 20, 1994 stamped "Master Set Second Pass." Contains holograph corrections. 133 pages (138 leaves) plus 3 post-it notes and 1 page cover letter from Vincent Janoski to McCarthy. January 31, 1994 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Cities of the Plain [screenplay], undated
  Series Desription
  Drafts and fragments for an unproduced screenplay of Cities of the Plain. McCarthy reworked it as a novel published in 1998.
  - Treatment. Typescript with holograph corrections. 19 leaves, undated (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - "El Paso / Juarez" treatment. Typescript. 16 leaves, undated (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Synopsis and McCarthy bio (2 copies). Photocopy. 6 leaves, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Characters in order of appearance (2 copies). Photocopy. 4 leaves, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Drafts, undated
    - Holograph pages 18-62 on notebook paper. 46 leaves, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Typescript draft with holograph corrections. Incomplete, numbered 1-17; 63-127 (83 leaves), undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Typescript draft, very lightly corrected. 174 pages, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Photocopy of 79 pages from previous draft with holograph corrections. Contains some typescript pages and 3 pages of holograph notes. Incomplete, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Photocopy and typescript pages, heavily corrected. 208 pages (246 leaves), undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Printout draft with penciled page numbers. No corrections. 156 pages (156 leaves), undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Printout draft with penciled page numbers. No corrections. 215 pages (216 leaves), undated (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy draft with holograph corrections in pencil. 196 pages (205 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Shooting script. Photocopy with minor holograph corrections. 128 pages (129 leaves), undated (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Fragments, undated
    - Photocopy pages plus "note to stenographer." 61 leaves, undated (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Typescript and photocopy pages with holograph corrections. 13 leaves, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Typescript pages with holograph corrections. 33 leaves, undated (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Typescript and photocopy pages with Spanish phrases. 47 leaves, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Spanish phrases. 105 leaves, undated (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Cities of the Plain, 1998, undated
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence, notes, drafts, fragments, proofs, and production material relating to McCarthy's 1998 novel, Cities of the Plain.
  - Correspondence, 1998
    - Kevin to Gary [Fisketjon]. TNS [Internal Knopf memo], 1 page, February 19, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      Sending lightly copyedited manuscript for author's review.
    - G[ary Fisketjon] to McCarthy. Saturday, ALS, 1 page, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
      Sending first 200 pages along with notations.
    - Loose pages of holograph notes and queries, 5 leaves, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Notes, undated
    - Spiral-bound notebook titled "West" with post-it note on cover marked "Cities." 14 holograph pages and 1 piece of note paper laid-in, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Holograph, typescript, and photocopy pages in folder labeled "Cities – notes and pages." 39 leaves, plus folder, undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Loose-leaf pages of holograph notes, 9 leaves, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Drafts, 1998, undated
    - Typescript. Heavily corrected in pencil. 348 pages (397 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
      1; 1-28; 28a; 29; 32-34; 36-70; 72-75; 75(insert); 76-82; 83a; 107a; 108-117; 117a; 118-119; 119a; 120-126; 128; 122x; insert; [no #]; 136-140; 140; 140; 141-145; 145x; 146; 146a; 147; 147a; 148-198; 198(1)-198(11); 199-221; 254; 254; [no #]; 223; 222; 224-226; 259; 227-236; 232a; 238-249; 249a; 250-255; 255a; 256-266; 300; 267-269; 303; 270-271; 271(1)-271(2); 308a; 271(3); 285-288; [no #]; 289-291; 272-284; 292-310; 312; 312a; Z(1)-Z(18); 1; Z(19)-Z(29); Z(31)-Z(32); Zx3; Z(33); Zx1; Zx2; 12; 66; 85; 102; 113; 208; 255-257; 257-260; 270; 273; 275; 278; 313; 318; 348
    - Typescript. Heavily corrected in pencil. 393 pages (394 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
      1-11; 11a; 12-39; 39a; 40-43; 43a; 44; 44a; 45-58; 58a; 58b; 59-66; 66a; 67-76; 76a; 76bx; 76b; 77-85; 85a; 85a; 86-101; 101x; 102-127; 127a; 128-140; 140a; 140a; 141-166; 166a; 167-200; 201a; 201-233; 233x; 234-259/260; 261-268; 268a; 269-271; 271a; 272-282; 282a; 283-294; 294a; 295-299; 299a; 300-313; 313a; 314-315; 315x; 315a; 315b; 316-331; 331a; 332-339; 339a; 340-347; 347x; 348; 349-355; 355a; 356; 356a; 357-369; 369a; 370-389; 389x; 389y; 390; 390a; 391; 391x; 392-393
    - Box for draft in box 71, folder 6. White Joe's Copies box. Marked "original" in black in, "Cities" in pencil, and "original mss w/ corr's by CM" in blue ink (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Printout draft with holograph corrections in green ink and pencil. 363 pages. (Housed in 2 parts), undated
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-200 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 200-363 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Printout draft (incomplete) numbered 1-200 with holograph corrections in ref ink and pencil, undated (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Printout draft with corrections in orange ink and pencil. 410 pages. (Housed in 2 parts), undated
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-209 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 210-410 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Box for drafts in box 73, folders 1-2. White Copy Box marked "Cities – Final w/ed" in pencil (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Printout draft (incomplete) numbered 1-200 with minor holograph corrections. Marked "Dec 20. All red & green corrections done 1-200 except p. 97", undated (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Printout draft. 411 pages housed in 3 parts. The corrected pages in part 3 fill in the gaps in parts 1 and 2, undated
      - Part 1 of 3 numbered 1-210 (with gaps). (146 leaves) (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Part 2 of 3 numbered 213-411 (with gaps). (135 leaves) (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Part 3 of 3 numbered 2-406 (fill the gaps in parts 1 and 2). (130 leaves) (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Box for drafts in box 74, folders 2-4. White Joe's Copies box marked "Final Feb 98" in pencil (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Printout draft with no corrections. 411 pages. (Housed in 2 parts), undated
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-210 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 211-411 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Box for drafts in box 75 folders 2-3. White Joe's Copies box marked "org Cities of the Plain" in pencil (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Fragments, undated
    - Holograph, typescript, and photocopy pages of notes and drafts for the Epilogue. 103 leaves plus annotated folder, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - "Epilogue" notes and drafts, undated
      - Typescript pages with holograph corrections, numbered "z" pages (36 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Printout pages with holograph corrections, numbered 1-40 (42 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Printout pages with only Spanish accent marks corrected in pencil, numbered 1-49 (49 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Printout pages with no corrections, numbered 362a-410 (49 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Printout pages numbered 46, 241, 261, 299, 323, 326, 343. (7 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Spanish phrases. Photocopy pages in manila folder marked "Spanish." (85 leaves), undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Proofs, 1998
    - Setting copy. Printout with setting notes in red; copyedited in green; CM corrections in purple, 411 pages (416 leaves), undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Page proofs with corrections, "First Pass," 291 pages (297 leaves) (Housed in 2 parts), March 5, 1998
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-151, plus front matter (157 leaves) (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 152-291 (140 leaves) (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Page proofs with corrections in blue and brown ink, "Second Pass Master," 298 pages plus front matter and three internal Knopf memos, each 1 page dated March 17, 1998; March 20, 1998; and March 25, 1998. 308 leaves (Housed in 2 parts)
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-152, plus front matter and three TNS (162 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 153-298 (146 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Page proofs with corrections in blue, "Third Pass," 298 pages plus front matter and internal Knopf Memo, TNS, 306 leaves. (Housed in 2 parts), March 26, 1998
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-152, plus front matter and TNS (160 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 153-398 (146 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Page proofs, PDF printout, no corrections. 298 pages (304 leaves) (Housed in 2 parts), March 30, 1998
      - Part 1 of 2 numbered 1-152, plus front matter (158 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Part 2 of 2 numbered 153-298 (146 leaves) (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Production Materials, undated
    - Picador edition jacket proof and printed promotional card, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
- No Country for Old Men [screenplay], 1987, undated
  Drafts and fragments for an unproduced screenplay of No Country for Old Men. McCarthy reworked it as a novel published in 2005. Ethan and Joel Coen eventually adapted it for the screen in 2007.
  - Drafts, undated
    - Photocopy of heavily corrected typescript, 102 pages (104 leaves), July 12, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Typescript, heavily corrected in pencil, 169 pages (189 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
      1-2; 2a; 3; 3a; 4-5; 5a-5c; 5c1-5c3; 5da; 5db; 5fc; 6-21; 21a; 22-26; 26a; 27-31; 31a; 31b; 32-36; 36a; 37-63; 63a; 64-67; 67a; 68-101; 101a; 102-103; 103a; 104-107; 107a; 108; 108a; 108b; 109-126; 126a; 127-137; 137a; 139-140; 140a; 141-145; 145a-145d; 146-153; 153a; 154-157; 157a; 158-169
    - Photocopy of previous corrected typescript, with alternate page 1, and several variations in pagination. 169 pages (153 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
      1; 1-2; 2; 3; 3a; 4-5; 5a-5c; 5cc; 5c1-5c3; 5da; 5da; 5eb; 5fc; 6-11; 11-14; 18; 20-21; 24; 26; 26a; 29; 31a-31b; 34; 40-46; 49; 60; 63-67; 71; 73-74; 77-80; 84-86; 90-91; 95-100; 100-101; 101a; 102-103; 103a; 104-107; 107a; 108; 108a-108b; 107-126; 127-132; 132; 133; 133-137; 139-140; 140a; 141-145 145a-145d; 146-153; 153a; 154-157; 157a; 158-162; 164-165; 165; 166-169
    - Printout draft with minor pencil corrections, 104 pages, undated
    - Printout draft with no corrections, 104 pages, plus manila folder marked "No Country – old orig script", undated (Box 79, Box 5)
  - Fragments, undated
    - Typescript pages with holograph corrections, 28 leaves, plus folder labeled "No Country", undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Typescript pages with holograph corrections, 66 leaves, plus folder marked "No Country", undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
- No Country for Old Men, 2003-2007, undated
  Correspondence, notes, drafts, fragments, proofs, production materials, and reviews for McCarthy's 2005 novel, No Country for Old Men.
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005, undated
    - Della Ulibarri invoice for typing services, (2 leaves), November 22, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Gary Fisketjen to McCarthy, ANS (1 leaf) plus 6 page proofs, January 3, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Amanda Urban to McCarthy, TLS (1 leaf) plus 26 page enclosure, March 4, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Barry [King] to McCarthy, TL (3 leaves) plus 5 photocopy pages and folder, undated (Box 80, Folder 3)
      Discusses and provides suggestions for ms pages relating to Chigurh's treatment of his injuries.
  - Notes, 2007, undated
    - Texas sheriff notes, photocopy and typescript pages, plus a pencil rendering of a main street scene "courtesy Benny Rodriquez." (18 leaves), undated (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Page reference and notes, holograph and photocopy pages in folder marked "Bell March '07." (5 leaves), 2007 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - "No Country last notes. Country talk…" Typescript pages with annotations. (3 leaves) plus folder, undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Drafts, 2003-2004, undated
    - Typescript with holograph corrections in pencil. (379 leaves) Irregular pagination, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
      [no #]; 1a; 2-12; 13a; 14-20; 20a; 21-43; 43a; 43b; 44-45; 45a; 46-55x; 55-58; 58a; 58b; 59-64; 64a; 64b; 65-77; 77a; 78-81; 83-84; 82; 85a; 86-99; 99a; 100-112; 112a; 113-115; 115a; 116-120; 120a; 121-126; 126a; 127-136; 136a; 137-159; 159a-159l; 166a; 159a-159z; 160-162; 162a; 163-168; 170-178; 178a; 179-196; 199; 197-198; 200-214; 214a; 215-235; 235a; 236-241; 241; 241-243; 243; 243; 243; 243a; 244; [2 no #]; 247-256; 257a; 257-260; 261a; 261; 263; 264-271; 271a; 272-282; 282a; 283-293; 222x; 182a; 284; 62x; 247a; 127x; 282x; [no #]; 167a; 167b; 168; 169; [170]; 254-255; 255x; 256-257; 257a; 257b; 307x; 300; 300a; 228; 96x; 63a.
    - Typescript and photocopy draft with holograph corrections in pencil. Various sections. (271 leaves), undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Partial photocopy of previous draft. No holograph corrections; fewer pages, in folder labeled "Tickets" and marked [by typist] "rec'd 10/21/03 @ 4:30." 167 pages (182 leaves), 2003 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Printout draft with holograph corrections. Numbered: 1-89; 83- 196. 196 pages (203 leaves), May 10, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Photocopy of corrected printout draft #A. Holograph corrections begin on p. 191, with note: "1st proofreading May 12, '04…Della has xrox pp. 191-264." Numbered: 1-82; 81-200; 201a; 201-241; 242a; 242-264. 264 pages (268 leaves plus folder), 2004 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Printout draft with holograph in pencil. "Late draft." 308 pages (328 leaves). Irregular pagination, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
      1-62; 62a; 62b; 64-96; 96x; 97-127; 127x; 128-166; 166a; 167; 167a-167c; 168-182; 182a; 183-221; 222x; 222-247; 247a; 248-255; 255x; 256-257; 257a; 257b; 258-282; 282x; 283-297; 298x-1; 298x-2; 298x-3; 298-300; 300a; 301-307; 307x; 308
    - Photocopy of printout draft with minor holograph corrections in pencil. "Late draft – after pencil corr's." 320 pages, undated (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Photocopy of printout draft with minor holograph corrections in pencil. "X of final draft – a few corr's (in Xerox)." 319 pages, undated (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Printout draft with minor holograph corrections in pencil. "Final draft w/some pencil corr's June 10 2004." 319 pages, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Printout draft with minor holograph corrections in pencil. "Final draft. Orig of 2 copies sent to NY June 10 04." 320 pages, undated (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Printout draft with minor holograph corrections in pencil. In folder marked "June 12 '04 / Shred (old x's)." 342 pages, June 12, 2004 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Printout draft with no corrections. "Final draft Nov 22 no corr's." 341 pages, undated (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Photocopy draft with editorial annotations in red ink. Marked "Due 15 Nov [Mon]." 320 pages, undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Fragments, 2004, undated
    - Typescript pages with holograph corrections in pencil. Includes McCarthy's list of alternate names for Chigurh, including Chingo, Chigaret, Chigrey, Chingore and Chigore. Labeled "_____Country (Texas, 1984)." (3 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Typescript pages 184a-184b; 239a-239h; 242a with holograph corrections in pencil. In folder marked "No Country - new pp. (All x'd and into MS)." 11 leaves plus folder, undated (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Typescript pages in section titled "Prison" in folder marked "Prison + misc (n/useable)." Corrected. 19 leaves plus folder, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Typescript pages in section titled "Motel." Holograph corrections. (8 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Various corrected typescript pages (11 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages with no holograph corrections. (135 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages of sections apparently unrelated to No Country, titled "Long John," "QM," "Journal," "Quarry," and "Kid." (8 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages (149 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Photocopy of notes written on Santa Fe Institute letterhead with pencil notations (3 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages 1-70a, no holograph corrections in folder marked "Bell/Moss." (81 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages (100 leaves plus annotated folder), undated (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Photocopy of corrected typescript pages (13 leaves), undated (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Typescript and printout pages with holograph corrections (32 leaves), undated (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Typescript and photocopy pages (3 leaves), undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Printout pages numbered 1-80, no holograph corrections. (80 leaves), undated (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Printout pages of Sheriff Bell's monologues from chapter openings. Minor holograph corrections in pencil. In folder marked "All monologues marked I through IX #A draft." (39 leaves plus folder), undated (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Printout pages numbered 1-82 with holograph corrections in pencil. Includes some typescript pages. In folder marked "#A pp. 1-82." (83 leaves plus folder), undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Printout pages numbered 81-190 [#A], with minor holograph corrections in pencil. (110 leaves plus folder), undated (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Photocopy of corrected printout pages 83-190 in folder marked "Copy of 2nd batch (pp. 83-190) of pp from Della w/ corr's for her. She has this (May 7 04)." (108 leaves plus folder), undated (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Photocopy of corrected printout pages 191-264, (76 leaves), May 12 2004 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Printout pages numbered 221-308 with holograph corrections in pencil. Note on first page, "#A. Della has Xerox of this, May 18, '04." (89 leaves plus folder), 2004 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Proofs, 2005
    - Setting copy. No corrections. Includes photocopy note from McCarthy to Gary [Fisketjen] and Jan 5, 2005 internal memo. 341 pages (349 leaves) (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Rough page proofs, "First Pass - uncorrected." 306 pages (320 leaves), February 8, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Rough page proofs, "First Pass – original with pencil corrections." 306 pages (320 leaves plus folder), February 8, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Page proofs, with holograph corrections in pencil. 309 pages (320 leaves), March 29, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 3)